A Guide to the Richmond Annexation Files 1942-1976
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- City of Richmond v. United States of America n.d., 1969-1975
  - Finding of Fact 1972 (Box-folder 8.12)
  - Finding of Fact (Proposed) and Conclusion Law 1974 (Box-folder 8.13)
  - Fiscal Analysis of County's Settlement for Annexation 1975 (Box-folder 8.14)
  - Fiscal and Utilities Information 1975 (Box-folder 8.15)
  - General Assembly Action, Review of 1975 (Box-folder 8.16)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/5 Ansers 11/3, Defendant's Witnesses 1975 (Box-folder 8.17)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/15 Answers 12/30 1975 (Box-folder 8.18)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/15 Answers 10/16 1975 (Box-folder 8.19)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/15 Answers 11/20 1975 (Box-folder 8.20)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/18 Answers 10/14 1975 (Box-folder 8.21)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 9/18 Answers 10/16 1975 (Box-folder 8.22)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 11/11 Answers 11/26 1975 (Box-folder 8.23)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 11/20 Answers 12/15 1975 (Box-folder 8.24)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 12/17 Answers 1/5 1975-1976 (Box-folder 8.25)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 12/2 Answers 12/16 1975 (Box-folder 8.26)
  - Interrogatories Propounded 12/11 Answers 12/24 1975 (Box-folder 8.27)
  - Interrogatories and Other Motions n.d. (Box-folder 8.28)
  - Interrogatory Section B #10 n.d. (Box-folder 8.29)
  - Interrogatory Section B #11-12 n.d. (Box-folder 8.30)
  - Interrogatory Section C #4 1973 (Box-folder 9.1)
  - Legal Forms n.d. (Box-folder 9.2)
  - Master's Report, Motion for Rejection and Modification n.d. (Box-folder 9.3)
  - Master's Report, Objections to (Citations) n.d. (Box-folder 9.4)
  - Master's Report, Objections to n.d. (Box-folder 9.5)
  - Master's Report, Originals and Duplicates of Objections 1976 (Box-folder 9.6)
  - Miscellaneous 1975-1976 (Box-folder 9.7)
  - Miscellaneous (Interrogatories) n.d. (Box-folder 9.8)
  - Miscellaneous (Interrogatories and City Exhibits) n.d. (Box-folder 9.9)
  - Notes, Conference 1975 (Box-folder 9.10)
  - Notes (Sinsabaugh, Kathy) 1975 (Box-folder 9.11)
  - Objections, Pre-Hearing Memo 1973 (Box-folder 9.12)
  - Petition for Writ of Certiorari 1972 (Box-folder 9.13)
  - Petition for Writ of Certiorari Appendix n.d. (Box-folder 9.14)
  - Plaintiff's List of Witnesses with credentials n.d. (Box-folder 9.15)
  - Pleadings n.d. (Box-folder 9.16)
  - Point C (General Expenditure Allocation) n.d. (Box-folder 9.17)
  - Point (Population Data) 1975 (Box-folder 9.18)
  - Printed Briefs (1 of 4) (Box-folder 9.19)
  - Printed Briefs (2 of 4) (Box-folder 9.20)
  - Printed Briefs (3 of 4) n.d. (Box-folder 10.1)
  - Printed Briefs (4 of 4) n.d. (Box-folder 10.2)
  - Proceedings 7/23 1973 (Box-folder 10.3)
  - Proceedings 10/15 (I-258) 1973 (Box-folder 10.4)
  - Proceedings 10/16 (260-380) 1973 (Box-folder 10.5)
  - Proceedings 10/16 (381-568) 1973 (Box-folder 10.6)
  - Proceedings 10/17 (570-737) 1973 (Box-folder 10.7)
  - Proceedings 12/19 1973 (Box-folder 10.8)
  - Proceedings 1/12 (1-192) 1973 (Box-folder 10.9)
  - Proceedings 1/13 (193-402) 1976 (Box-folder 10.10)
  - Proceedings 1/14 (403-617) 1976 (Box-folder 10.11)
  - Proceedings 1/15 (620-915) 1976 (Box-folder 10.12)
  - Proceedings 1/16 (918-1144/1215) 1976 (Box-folder 10.13)
  - Proceedings 1/19 (1216-1432) 1976 (Box-folder 10.14)
  - Proceedings 1/20 (1433-1511) 1976 (Box-folder 10.15)
  - Remand (1 of 5) 1975 (Box-folder 10.16)
  - Remand (2 of 5) 1975 (Box-folder 11.1)
  - Remand (3 of 5) 1975 (Box-folder 11.2)
  - Remand (4 of 5) 1975 (Box-folder 11.3)
  - Remand (5 of 5) 1975 (Box-folder 11.4)
  - Reply to Objections 1974 (Box-folder 11.5)
  - Richmond Police Bureau Organizational and Operational Analysis n.d. (Box-folder 11.6)
  - Richmond Forward 1966 (Box-folder 11.7)
  - Sunday Closing Law 1974 (Box-folder 11.8)
  - Urban Analysis (Murphy, Tom) 1975 (Box-folder 11.9)
  - Wards--Proposed 1971, Oversized (Box-folder 11.10)
- Supporting Documentation n.d., 1942,1969-1972
  - ACIR State Legislation Program n.d. (Box-folder 11.11)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations Fifteen Year Report 1974 (Box-folder 11.12)
  - Allocation of Expenditures and Departmental Revenue 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11.13)
  - Allocation--School (Budget Notes) 1976 (Box-folder 11.14)
  - Annual Report of the Richmond Public Schools 1964-1973 (Box-folder 11.15)
  - Annual Report of the Richmond Public Schools 1969-1972 (Box-folder 11.16)
  - Annual Report of the Richmond Public Schools 1971-1972 (Box-folder 11.17)
  - Annual Report of the Richmond Public Schools 1972-1974 (Box-folder 11.18)
  - Annual Report of the Richmond Public Schools 1973-1974 (Box-folder 12.1)
  - Big Government 1975 (Box-folder 12.2)
  - Bradley vs Richmond School Board Motions and Supporting Documentation 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12.3)
  - Bradley v. Richmond School Board Brief for Appellees 1972 (Box-folder 12.4)
  - Bradley v Richmond School Board US Court of Appeals 1972 (Box-folder 12.5)
  - Bradley v. Richmond School Board Brief for Appellants 1972 (Box-folder 12.6)
  - Bradley vs Richmond School Board Appendix 1972 (Box-folder 12.7)
  - Bradley v. Richmond School Board Memorandum 1972 (Box-folder 12.8)
  - Budget--Annual (Annexation Supplement) 1969-1970 (Box-folder 12.9)
  - Budget--Annexation Area Composite 1969-1975 (Box-folder 12.10)
  - Budget--Proposed 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12.11)
  - Budget--Adopted 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12.12)
  - Budget--Adopted 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12.13)
  - Budget--Chesterfield County 1974-1976 (Box-folder 12.14)
  - Budget--Adopted 1975-1976 (Box-folder 12.15)
  - Budget--Adopted 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13.1)
  - Budget--Adopted 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13.2)
  - City Council Dockett 1974 (Box-folder 13.3)
  - City Council Dockett 1975 (Box-folder 13.4)
  - City Planning Commission Minutes January-June 1974 (Box-folder 13.5)
  - City Planning Commission Minutes July-December 1974 (Box-folder 13.6)
  - City Planning Commission Minutes January-April 1975 (Box-folder 13.7)
  - City Plannign Commission Minutes May-December 1975 (Box-folder 13.8)
  - Classification, Assessments and Taxation according to use of Real Estate 1974 (Box-folder 13.9)
  - Comparative Population data for Two Chesterfield County Areas 1958-1964 (Box-folder 13.10)
  - Financial Report of the Director of Finance 1970 (Box-folder 13.11)
  - Financial Report of the Director of Finance 1971 (Box-folder 13.12)
  - Financial Report of the Director of Finance 1972 (Box-folder 13.13)
  - Financial Report of the Director of Finance 1973 (Box-folder 13.14)
  - Financial Report on Department of Public Utilities 1975 (Box-folder 13.15)
  - Five Year Transit Development Program for the Counties of Chesterfield and Henrico 1975 (Box-folder 13.16)
  - Fundamentals of Municipal Bonds (Box-folder 13.17)
  - Gross Vacant Land 1942 (Box-folder 13.18)
  - Impact of Annexation on City Finances 1973 (Box-folder 13.19)
  - Master Plan of Land Use, Community Facilities and Trafficways 1964 (Box-folder 13.20)
  - Metro Richmond Figures n.d. (Box-folder 13.21)
  - Organization and Management Study: Richmond Public Schools 1973 (Box-folder 13.22)
  - Personnel Analysis of the City of Richmond 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14.1)
  - Personnel Analysis for the City of Richmond 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14.2)
  - Pitfalls in issuing Municipal Bonds 1963 (Box-folder 14.3)
  - Pupil Transportation 1971-1974 (Box-folder 14.4)
  - Reforming the Virginia Property Tax v. 1 1974 (Box-folder 14.5)
  - Report of the Auditor of Public Accounts on the Comparative Cost of City Government 1968-1972 (Box-folder 14.6)
  - Report of Auditor of Public Accounts on Comparative Cost of City Government 1973 (Box-folder 14.7)
  - Report of the Judicial Council of Virginia 1967-1972 (Box-folder 14.8)
  - School Board Budget 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14.9)
  - School Board Budget 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14.10)
  - School Board Report on Examination 1970-1973 (Box-folder 14.11)
  - Statistical Data on Richmond Public Schools 1975 (Box-folder 14.12)
  - Telephone Directory 1975 (Box-folder 14.13)
  - Transit Development Program 1976 (Box-folder 14.14)
  - Virginia School Census 1971, 1974 (Box-folder 14.15)
  - Voting Rights Case: Answers from Departments and Agencies 1976 (Box-folder 14.16)
  - Voting Rights Case Survey I n.d. (Box-folder 14.17)
  - Voting Rights Case Survey II n.d. (Box-folder 14.18)
  - Voting Trends in Councilmanic Elections 1960-1962 (Box-folder 14.19)